<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-29T23:33:16+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Petrov’s farm</title><subtitle>The best food for your table!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Our commitments!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our commitments!" /><published>2018-11-12T22:30:34+02:00</published><updated>2018-11-12T22:30:34+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Petrov-s-farm/post/">&lt;div class=&quot;post&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        We are committed to continuing  longest operating sustainable farm and providing you food, fiber and farm products to feel good about.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        Every morning at daybreak, our sheep wake to graze freely in spacious fields of rich, unspoiled pastures so we can bring you the very best in delicious, all-natural lamb - just as we have for more than 100 year.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        Throughout our history, we have always taken great pride in our commitment to operating a natural, ethical and sustainable farm.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        We understand the importance of the health of our livestock, the preservation of the land that feeds us, and the well-being of the people who help us bring our product to market.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        We treat our flock with the utmost respect and work diligently to promote whole animal butchery as to not waste the precious resources of food and fiber that they have given us.
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div&gt;
        We believe the tender treatment of our animals leads to a better product.
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are committed to continuing longest operating sustainable farm and providing you food, fiber and farm products to feel good about. Every morning at daybreak, our sheep wake to graze freely in spacious fields of rich, unspoiled pastures so we can bring you the very best in delicious, all-natural lamb - just as we have for more than 100 year. Throughout our history, we have always taken great pride in our commitment to operating a natural, ethical and sustainable farm. We understand the importance of the health of our livestock, the preservation of the land that feeds us, and the well-being of the people who help us bring our product to market. We treat our flock with the utmost respect and work diligently to promote whole animal butchery as to not waste the precious resources of food and fiber that they have given us. We believe the tender treatment of our animals leads to a better product.</summary></entry></feed>